

# Marvin Santiago Henriquez Bertel

Software Engineer

#### Profile

Systems engineer passionate about web development focused and trained to provide the best user experience with excellent criteria in design, construction and execution of technology projects with the desire to continue learning and overcome new challenges.

## Employment History

APP DEVELOPER OMNICHANNEL at Olimpica S.A., Barranquilla

July 2021 — Present

Olimpica's app front-end developer and supervisor of the correct operation in the different sales channels.

Frontend mobile developer at Livery Colombia., Barranquilla

July 2020 — July 2021

Mobile application development for users and delivery couriers in React native.

### Freelancer at Labbel, Barranquilla

January 2020 — June 2020

Frontend developer for an application called apolo made with vuejs and nodejs which is a service manager using services from third parties such as cloudinary for image storage.

## Education

High School, Instituto Pedagógico de Maicao, Maicao

February 2010 — November 2015

Systems and Computer Engineer, Universidad del Norte, Barranquilla

January 2016 — November 2020



## Courses

Master en Frameworks JavaScript: Aprende Angular, React, Vue., Udemy

### ■ References

Mauricio Maldonado

+57 302 4241105

**Stevens Correa** 

+57 321 5362088

#### **Details**

Cra 39 #75b - 38 Apto 1303 Barranquilla Colombia +57 3014039187 marvinshb@gmail.com

Date / Place of birth

11/10/1999 Maicao

Nationality

Colombian

#### Links

LinkedIn Portfolio

#### **Skills**

React Js

Node Js

JavaScript

HTML

CSS Java

React Native

Angular

MongoDB

SQL

flutter

Git

Languages

Spanish; Castilian

English

# **Y** Extra-curricular activities

Member of the Universidad del Norte soccer team, Barranquilla February 2020 — June 2020

Voleyball team member at Universidad del Norte, Barranquilla August 2019 — November 2019

#### **Hobbies**

Play sports mainly soccer, watch movies, listen to music and learn more and more about web development.